

CONTACT

- +306988215196
- ✓ kostaskamperis96@gmail.com
- P Eleftheroupoli Dimadi 19b

SKILLS

- Programming Languages:
 JavaScript, Python, C, C++,
 C#
- Web Development: HTML, CSS
- Tools: OpManager, Paessler PRTG, Citrix, Active
 Directory, Veeam, Azure,
 Kaspersky Suite, Git,
 GitHub, npm, Microsoft
 Office, Windows OS, Linux,
 VS Code, Al
- Networking: Network troubleshooting configuration and support
- Soft Skills: Problem-solving, critical thinking, collaboration, adaptability, continuous learning

LANGUAGES

- Greek (Native)
- English (Fluent-C2)
- German (Intermediate-B1)

KAMPERIS KONSTANTINOS

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER | IT SUPPORT SPECIALIST

PROFILE

Highly motivated IT Support Specialist with two years of experience in the tech industry and a solid foundation in Electrical and Computer Engineering. Currently enhancing my programming skills while exploring software testing and quality assurance. Passionate about automation, troubleshooting, and learning industry-standard testing methodologies to transition into a Junior Developer or Software Engineer in Test role.

You can track some of my recent activity on my ongoing web portfolio project here.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Support Specialist / ServiceDesk

OCT.2022 - OCT.2024

Boss Info AG | Kavala, Greece

- Monitoring (NOC) all internal and external (customers) Infrastructure as well as Security & Backup incidents.
- Maintenance and active development of the monitoring solution and associated processes.
- First level response & support (SW & HW) internal & external.
- Opening and resolving incidents in Navision ERP software.
- Internal administrative tasks.
- Knowledge management implementation and maintenance.
- Participating in the planning and execution of bi-weekly sprints using the Scrum framework.
- Documentation of processes and best practices.
- Participating in the conception of processes and features.
- Constructing and using scripts for automation purposes using PowerShell and Python.

Exam Invigilator

JUN.2020-APR.2023

TÜV HELLAS | Eastern Macedonia and Thrace, Greece

 Working part-time in examinations prepared by Tuv Hellas, as the company's representative and exam invigilator I developed my communication skills through explaining the digital examination process, troubleshooting any IT problems and maintaining the proper conduct of the examination in a professional manner.

EDUCATION

Master of Engineering - Meng, Electrical and Computer Engineering

2014 - 2022

Democritus University Of Thrace

 Thesis: "Autonomous energy management for EV charging station with PV"